Krzysztof Gasik

Software Developer



Personal Info

Email

kgasik@gmail.com

Phone

506229209

Skills

React

Javascript

TypeScript

Redux

RTK Query

CSS

SASS

NPM

GIT

RWD

Node.js

jQuery

Linux

Skilled software development proffesional with 4 years in web development.

What are my current activities? Rewriting old applications to use React with TypeScript. Unit and Integration tests done with Jest and React Testing Library, E2E in cypress.

Collaborating with team members to produce better and cleaner code. Meetings with Software Architects and Designers.

My current stack is React with TypeScript, combined with GIT, Jenkins, Gerrit. Redux for state managment and RTK Query for api calls.

Work History

2022-01

Software Developer

- present

Nokia Solutions and Networks sp. z o.o., Wrocław

- Discussed issues with team members to provide resolution and apply best practices.
- Participated in software field testing to verify performance of developed projects.
- · Designed reusable and reliable code
- · Updating customer documentation

2020-04

Frontend Developer

- 2021-12

Telewizja Puls sp z.o.o, Warsaw

Creating content and adjusting it to designes (PSD files), work with content (provided by Marketing team) in Drupal CMS and applying them in websites belonging to Telewizja Puls.

Responsibility for the frontend layer and adjusting it with mobile first rule.

2011-06

DP Executive / DP Senior Executive

- 2020-03

Kantar Poland, Warsaw

Creating online surveys based on HTML / CSS / JS technologies. Creating survey support

tools:

- concept select (choosing words that match or do not match the given product, ads -
- created in jQuery)
- out of 10 (a tool to compare the last 10 product purchases created in jQuery)
- development and implementation of a new online survey appearance (layout)

consistent with the new logo for the entire branch in Poland

In my everyday projects I use the skills acquired at the Coders Lab school, which allows me

to create projects that meet the expectations of our clients, based on HTML $\!\!/$ CSS $\!\!/$ JS $\!\!/$

jQuery.

Education

2021-07

IT, none

- 2021-12

Szkoła Reacta, Warsaw

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy which I advertised.

Languages

English - C1

Polish - C2

2018-11 - 2019-06 2012-10 - 2013-06	IT, none Coders Lab, Warsaw
	Finance and Banking, graduate studies
	Warsaw University of Life Sciences, Warsaw
2005-10 - 2008-06	Public Administration, bachelor
	School of Computer Science, Management and Administration, Warsaw

Projects

2021-07 - 2021-08	Frontend Developer
	My portfolio
	https://krzysztofgasik.github.io/Portfolio/
2020-12 - 2021-04	Frontend Developer
	New version of website for TV Puls
	https://tvpuls.pl/

Courses

2023-11	End-to-End JavaScript Testing with Cypress.io
2023-11	React: Testing and Debugging
2023-11	TypeScript Essential Training
2023-04	Critical Thinking
2023-03	Giving and Receiving Feedback
2022-10	Builiding Modern Projects With React
2022-10	Express Essential Training
2022-10	Javascript: Closures
2022-10	Learning Node.js
2022-10	Learning Regular Expressions
2022-10	React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)
2022-10	React: Design Patterns
2022-10	React: Using TypeScript
2022-10	Understanding TypeScript
2019-11	Node.js: The Complete Guide to Build RESTful APIs (2018)
2019-09	Object-oriented Programming in JavaScript

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy which I advertised.